National Extension Association of Family and Consumer Sciences, New York Affiliate records, 1931-2005
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
National Extension Association of Family and Consumer Sciences, New York Affiliate records, 1931-2005.
3920
National Extension Association of Family and Consumer Sciences (U.S.)., New York Affiliate.
13 cubic ft.
Reports, minutes, correspondence, financial records, newsletters, and other records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Include reports, minutes, correspondence, financial records, and newsletters. Also records of their 50th anniversary celebration.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The organization originated as the New York State Home Demonstration Agents' Association in 1934. The organization later changed its name to the New York State Association of Extension Home Economists (NYSAEHE) and in 1995 it changed its name to the New York State Extension Association of Family and Consumer Sciences (NYSEAFCS).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Include reports, minutes, correspondence, financial records, and newsletters. Also records of their 50th anniversary celebration.
SUBJECTS
Names:
National Extension Association of Family and Consumer Sciences, New York Affiliate.; National Association of Extension Home Economists.; New York State Association of Home Demonstration Agents.
Subjects:
Home economics extension work--New York (State)
Form and Genre Terms:
Minutes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- History of the New York State Home Demonstration Agents Association, 1919-1965 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Minutes of meeting of Home Bureau Agents, 1918-1929 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Minutes of meeting of Home Bureau Agents, 1930-1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Minutes ("Doughbuster") of meeting of Home Bureau Agents, 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Minutes of meeting of Home Bureau Agents, 1950-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Minutes of meeting (Board of Directors) and Financial Report/Proposal Budget, 1957-1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- National Home Demonstration Agents' Association (NHDAA): papers and correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- NYSDAA: papers and correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- NYSDAA: papers and correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- NYSDAA: papers and correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- NHDAA: handbooks - Constitution, 1955, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- NYSDAA: Awards, "Contents of Corner Stone Box", 1950, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Book Shelf Memorial, 1944? (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Budgets, 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- "Doughbuster" handbook, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- NHDAA history, 1919-1952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- NHDAA history, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Initiations (ritual) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- List of names, 1914-1952 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- NYSHDA Board Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Minutes (Board of Directors), 1950-1956 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- NYSHDA Board Minutes, Correspondence, 1937-1952 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- NYSHDA Board Minutes, Correspondence, 1952-1956 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- NYSHDA Minutes and Correspondence, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- NYSHDA Minutes and Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- NYSHDA Minutes and Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- NYSHDA Minutes and Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Professional Improvement material, 1940-1959 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Radio and Newspaper (and TV) materials, 1953-1959 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Recognition Committee, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- State Agents Meeting - special session reports, 1955, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- HDA Reporter - newspapers, 1946-1953 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- History; correspondence, 1952-1959 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Meeting programs, 1953-1954, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- N.Y. State Reports, 1946-1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- List of Agents, 1936, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Constitution, 1947-1959 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Correspondence - Epsilon Sigma Phi, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- National HDA Association Handbook, NYS EDA Handbook, 1953, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- NYSHDA Handbook, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Pamphlets (handbook, history, etc.), 1947-1951 (Box 2)
- Minutes, Professional Improvement materials, 1959-1965 (Box 2)
- Agents, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
- Agents Extension Council, 1951-1953 (Box 2)
- Pertaining to Pfizer Award, 1956-1960 (Box 2)
- Pertaining to Martha Van Rensselaer Memorial Bookshelf, 1951-1965 (Box 2)
- Citizenship Committee Minutes, 1951-1965 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 2)
- Extension Studies Committee, 1956 (Box 2)
- Family Life Committee materials, 1954-1957 (Box 2)
- Floriculture Committee, 1954 (Box 2)
- Food and Nutrition Committee, 1954 (Box 2)
- Home Management Committee, 1954 (Box 2)
- Housing and Design Committee, 1955-1957 (Box 2)
- Institution Management Committee, 1954 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Committees, 1954-1957 (Box 2)
- Professional Improvement Committee, 1954-1958 (Box 2)
- Public Relations Committee, 1954-1958 (Box 2)
- Textiles and Clothing Committee, 1954-1958 (Box 2)
- Discussion Groups - report forms, 1961 (Box 2)
- Central District Agents meeting, 1955-1956 (Box 2)
- Eastern District, 1954-1956 (Box 2)
- Northern District, 1954-1956 (Box 2)
- Southern District, 1954-1956 (Box 2)
- Western District, 1954-1956 (Box 2)
- HD Program Committees, 1961-1964 (Box 2)
- National constitutions, 1949, 1952 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, etc., 1958-1960 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, etc., 1956-1958 (Box 2)
- Reports, Speeches, etc., 1956-1958 (Box 2)
- Handbook materials (general), 1959-1960 (Box 2)
- Handbook materials, 1963-1965 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, Board of Directors, etc., 1958-1959 (Box 2)
- Board of Directors materials, 1958-1960 (Box 2)
- HDAA materials, 1957-1959 (Box 2)
- Constitutions, 1939-1963 (Box 2)
- 1973 Fact Sheet, "EHE Reporter", 1973-1974 (Box 3)
- Annual Meetings (notices, information, etc.), pamphlets, 1973 (Box 3)
- Annual Meetings, correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 3)
- From "President's Notebook" - constitution, correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 3)
- From "President's Notebook" - committees, minutes, 1972-1974 (Box 3)
- Minutes, 1973 (Box 3)
- Para-professional awards and ENEP newsletter, 1973 (Box 3)
- Minutes, 1972 (Box 3)
- Professional Improvement materials, 1970 (Box 3)
- Correspondence, education materials, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
- Correspondence, program of work, etc., 1969-1970 (Box 3)
- Professional Improvement, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
- Professional Improvement, 1967-1968 (Box 3)
- Professional Improvement, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Professional Improvement, 1965-1966 (Box 3)
- Minutes, 1967-1969 (Box 3)
- Insurance Policy, 1973 (Box 3)
- From notebook: Awards, finances, minutes, etc., 1972-1974 (Box 3)
- From notebook: constitution, policies, 1973 (Box 3)
- From notebook: board of directors, minutes, 1971-1975 (Box 3)
- From notebook: correspondence, members, convention, 1971-1975 (Box 3)
- "EHE Reporters," national meeting materials, Minneapolis, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
- State presidents reports, 1974 (Box 3)
- National meeting Minneapolis, 1974 (Box 3)
- Minutes, 1974 (Box 3)
- Future of Association Study Committee (FSC), 1974 (Box 3)
- [reports, lists, minutes, etc.], 1974 (Box 3)
- Paraprofessional Award, 1974 (Box 3)
- National Meeting, presidents reports, 1975 (Box 3)
- Paraprofessional Award, 1975 (Box 3)
- Minutes (of various districts), 1975 (Box 3)
- Special Service Agent Award, 1975 (Box 3)
- National meeting materials (Boston, Portland), 1977 (Box 4)
- National meeting materials (Portland), 1976 (Box 4)
- Membership dues, 1977 (Box 4)
- Nominations, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
- Nominations, 1977 (Box 4)
- Honorary members, 1977 (Box 4)
- National registration, 1971-1977 (Box 4)
- Committees, 1979 (Box 4)
- Fall meeting, 1977 (Box 4)
- District minutes, 1976-1978 (Box 4)
- FSC "general", 1974-1977 (Box 4)
- FSC members and committees, committee reports, 1974-1976 (Box 4)
- FSC financial reports, 1974-1975 (Box 4)
- FSC minutes, 1973-1976 (Box 4)
- Public Awareness, 1977 (Box 4)
- Name Change, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
- State Committee Recruitment, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
- "Streamlining committees", 1978 (Box 4)
- State Committee Nominations Committee, 1976-1987 (Box 4)
- Reports, 1977 (Box 4)
- Information, reports, etc. (Omaha) 2 folders, 1978-1979 (Box 4)
- Lake Placid meeting, work program, 1974-1978 (Box 4)
- Correspondence, newsletter, notices, etc., 1964-1975 (Box 4)
- Programs, committees, meetings, etc., 1974-1976 (Box 4)
- TV spots, 1969 (Box 4)
- Public relations committee reports, 1973-1976 (Box 4)
- State newsletter ideas, 1974 (Box 4)
- Articles for Reporter, 1974-1975 (Box 4)
- Social Affairs - part 1, 1964-1975 (Box 4)
- Social Affairs - part 2, 1968-1974 (Box 4)
- Minutes, etc. (from binder 2, part 1), 1968-1970 (Box 4)
- Newsletters, etc. (binder 2, part 2), 1967-1970 (Box 4)
- EHE Reporter, 1970-1975 (Box 4)
- Constitution, Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1966-1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Guidelines for District Chairman - Southern District, 1967-1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Financial Reports, various district meetings, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- By-laws for Cooperative Extension Field Staff Council - 1972; Joint Association Committee, 1967-1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Plan of work; Reporter; meeting minutes, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Annual Report; Reporter; newsletter, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Minutes - various district meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Newspaper clippings, meeting minutes, 1973-1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Attendance and Dues; Meeting Minutes, meeting notices, 1968-1975 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Meeting notices; Correspondence, NYSAEHE Minutes, 1968-1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- NAEHE - 50th Anniversary Packet, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Programs (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Stationery (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Media Event and Specialists (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Pre session Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Budget and Finance (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Steering Committee (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Committee Minutes, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Committee List & Label, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Correspondence - In (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Correspondence - Out (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Other States (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Ag. 4-H Sea Grant (Box 6, Folder 14)
- First Times (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Publicity and Promotion (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Friendship Event (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Honorary Members (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Tours (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Hospitality (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Opening Ceremonies (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Elaine's Activities (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Workshops on the Move (Box 6, Folder 23)
- HEIB Meeting (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Ideas (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Response to The NYSAEHE Board (Box 6, Folder 26)
- NYSAEHE Board Minutes (Box 6, Folder 27)
- General Information (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Plans of Work (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Plans of Work, 1962-1990 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- 50th Anniversary - Committee, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- 50th Anniversary Material (Box 6, Folder 32)
- 50th Anniversary Material - Reporter, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- 50th Anniversary Material (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Membership Journal, 1949-1984 (Box 6)
- Membership Journal, 1959-1962 (Box 6)
- Procedures Handbook (Box 7)
- State Newsletter, 1979-1989 (Box 7)
- State Meetings, 1976-1988 (Box 7)
- Policy Handbook, 1976-1993 (Box 7)
- District Minutes, 1979-1983 (Box 7)
- Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1982-1988 (Box 7)
- Constitutions and By-laws, 1983-1986 (Box 7)
- Financial Records, 1983-1989 (Box 7)
- Directories and Membership Lists, 1984-1989 (Box 7)
- State Meeting (New York City), 1984 (Box 7)
- State Meeting (Painted Post), 1985 (Box 7)
- State Meeting (Saratoga Springs), 1986 (Box 7)
- General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1987-1989 (Box 7)
- Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 7)
- State Meeting (South Hampton), 1987 (Box 7)
- National Session (Pittsburgh, PA), 1988 (Box 7)
- Joint State Meeting - NYSAEHE/NYSAHEA (Syracuse), 1988 (Box 7)
- Endowed Chair, 1988 (Box 7)
- District Reports, 1988 (Box 7)
- Advisory Circle, 1989 (Box 7)
- Marketing Home Economics Campaign, 1989 (Box 7)
- National Meeting (Honolulu, HI), 1989 (Box 7)
- State Meeting (Niagara Falls), 1989 (Box 7)
- Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 7)
- Directory; 1993 Board Members, 1990-1995 (Box 7)
- State Conference - NYSAEHE, NYSHETA, NYSAHEA, 1990 (Box 7)
- Board of Directors Minutes, 1990 (Box 7)
- Correspondence, 1990 (Box 7)
- Professional Improvement/Recognition Committee, 1990 (Box 7)
- Eastern Region Presidents' Workshop, 1991 (Box 8)
- Board of Directors Minutes, 1991 (Box 8)
- Correspondence, 1991 (Box 8)
- NAEHE Business, 1991 (Box 8)
- Unification, 1991 (Box 8)
- HELM, 1991 (Box 8)
- Lake Placid Conference, 1991 (Box 8)
- Board of Directors Minutes, December 1991-1992 (Box 8)
- NAEHE Conference (Washington, DC), 1992 (Box 8)
- Correspondence, 1992 (Box 8)
- State Conference - NYSAEHE, NYSHETA, NYSAHEA, 1992 (Box 8)
- National Mission, Principles of Professional Practice, 1992 (Box 8)
- Extension Administration in the 90's, 1992 (Box 8)
- Procedures Handbook, 1992 (Box 8)
- Regional/National Business, 1992, 1994 (Box 8)
- Board of Directors Minutes, 1993 (Box 8)
- Correspondence, 1993 (Box 8)
- NYSCEE Professional Conference (Niagara Falls), 1993 (Box 8)
- Annual Session (Phoenix, AZ), 1993 (Box 8)
- Board of Directors Minutes, 1994 (Box 8)
- Correspondence, 1994 (Box 8)
- Honorary Membership/Retirees, 1994 (Box 8)
- Adoption of By-laws Procedures Manual, September 24, 1994 (Box 8)
- Souvenir Plate from Saratoga Conference, 1991 (Box 8)
- NAEHE Administrative Manual and By-laws, 1993 (Box 8)
- National Logo Masters (Box 8)
- Administrative Manual, 1995-1996 (Box 8)
- Board of Directors Minutes, 1996 (Box 8)
- Correspondence, 1996 (Box 8)
- Friendship/Welcome Event (Providence, RI), 1996 (Box 8)
- Board of Directors Minutes, 1997 (Box 8)
- Correspondence, 1997 (Box 8)
- NEAFCS New York - Presidents Notebook, 200-2001 (Box 9, Folder 1-5)
- NEAFCS New York - Conference Planning Committee, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- NEAFCS New York - Conference Planning Committee, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- NEAFCS New York - Conference Planning Committee, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- NEAFCS New York - Members, 1999-2003 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- "Extension Home Economics in Saratoga County" - by Mary Jane Ellis, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Awards Committee Correspondence, 1991-2005 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Board Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, etc., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, etc, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, etc, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, Plans of Work, etc, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Member Data, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Member Data Sheets, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Member Data, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Member Data, 1990, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Member Data Sheets, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Awards Committee Structure, c.a. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Committee Information, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Committee Work, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Committee Work, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Assorted Applications, Meeting Minutes, Descriptions, c.a. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Publication "Living and Learning", April, December 1998, February 1999 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Publication: Food and Family Well Being, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Articles and Correspondence Regarding Childcare, c.a. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Newspaper Clippings and Press Releases, 1981-1991 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- CD: RAPP Family Portraits: Grandfamilies Tell Their Stories, December 2005 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Nutrition Media Grant, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Youth at Risk Program Abstracts, 1993-1996 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- History of the National Association of Extension Home Economics, 1933-1975 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Photographs and Negatives, c.a. 1991 (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Photographs: Date Unknown (Box 10, Folder 65)
- Photographs, 1950s-2001 (Box 14, Folder 12-13)
- Membership Book, 1948-1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- List of Officers, 1967-1970 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- List of Officers, Minutes (NYSAEHE), Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Convention, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Officers Notebook-Minutes, Memos, Guidelines, Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 11, Folder 9-10)
- Committee Reports, List of Officers, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Committee Reports, List of Officers, Minutes, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Committee Reports, List of Officers, Minutes, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Committee Reports, List of Officers, Minutes, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Committee Reports, List of Officers, Minutes, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Committee Reports, List of Officers, Membership, Awards, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Committee Reports, List of Officers, Minutes, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Committee Reports, List of Officers, Minutes, Conferences, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Awards Dinner Programs, 1981,1985 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Committee Reports, Minutes, Fund Raising, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Committee Reports, List of Officers, Minutes, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Procedures Handbook, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Committee Reports, List of Officers, Minutes, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Committee Reports, List of Officers, Minutes, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Committee Reports, Minutes, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Unified Home Economists-Minutes, Matrix of Officers, 1990-1995 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Constitution and By-Laws, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Constitution, Board of Directors, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Board of Directors, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Constitution, Committees, Central Districts Agents' Meetings, Board of Directors, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Central Districts Agents' Meeting Minutes, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Central Districts Agents' Meeting Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- District Home Economics Agents' Meeting Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Constitution, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Constitution, Memos, Recruitment Reports, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Recruitment Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Constitution, Committee Reports, District Agents' Meetings, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Committee Reports, Memos, District Meeting Minutes, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Committee Reports, Memos, District Meeting Minutes, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Committee Reports and Memos, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Membership Lists, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Professional Improvement Committee, 1974-1979 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Professional Improvement Committee, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Committees, Constitution, Memos, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Professional Improvement Committee, 1975-1982 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- District Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Board of Directors Meetings, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 23-24)
- District Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Board of Directors Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Meeting Minutes, Membership, 1988-1988 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Newsletters, Correspondence, Membership Directory, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Committees, Constitution, Memos, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Meeting Minutes, Reports, Newsletters, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Memos, Reports, By-laws, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 34-36)
- Meeting Minutes, Memos, Reports, 199o (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Board Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- State Home Economics Conference for Organizational Leaders, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, Conference Information, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- By-Laws, Procedures Handbook, 1994-1994 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
- Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10-11)
- NEAFCS Member Handbook, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, Membership (from President's Notebook), 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 13-14)
- Meeting Minutes, Reports, Memos, Membership (from President's Notebook), 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 15-16)
- Membership Lists, 1971-1989 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Membership Directories, 1990-2002 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Membership Directories, 2003-2009 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Membership Lists, 1971-1989 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Public Relations, Personnel Issues, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Budgets, 1977-2008 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Financial Statements, 2001-2009 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 2006-2008 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Series I. Awards
  - NEAFCS Awards Application: Written News Category: Susan M. Figaro Grace, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - NEAFCS Awards Application: Florence Hall Awards Category: Susan M. Figaro Grace, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - NEAFCS Special Service Award Application: Karen Roberts Mort, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - NEAFCS Awards Application: Distinguished Service Award Category: Rosemary Hartman, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - NEAFCS Awards Application: Florence Hall Award Category: Deilee N. Calvert-Minor, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - NEAFCS Awards Application: Written News Category: Theresa Mayhew, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - NEAFCS Awards Application: Community Partnership Award for The Parenting Education Coalition: Isabelle Doran Jensen, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - NEAFCS Awards Application: New Professional Award Category: Lisa M. Millis, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - NEAFCS Awards Application: Radio Category: Virginia Gundlach Houseknecht, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - NEAFCS Awards Application: Community Partnership Award Category: Susan Figaro Grace, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - NEAFCS Awards Application: Environmental Award Category: Theresa Mayhew, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - NEAFCS Awards Application: Television Category: Susan M. Figaro Grace, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - NEAFCS Awards Application: 4-H Excellence in After School Programming: Linda Byster, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - NEAFCS Awards Application: Food Safety Award Category: Deilee N. Calvert-Minor, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - NEAFCS Awards Application: Television Video: Colleen M. Dewey-Wright, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - NEAFCS-NYA Carolyn O. Boegly Outstanding Leadership Award: Jeanne Winters, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - NEAFCS-NYA Friend of Extension Family and Consumer Sciences Award: Marc Sieben, Kerry Hunter, c.a. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - NEAFCS-NYA Friend fo Extension Family and Consumer Sciences Award: Richard J. Nunez, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - General Application Form: Environmental Education Award: Theresa C. Mayhew, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - General Application Form: Environmental Education Award: Faye O. Rosselle, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - General Application Form: Newsletters: Tanya Lipinski Wilkins, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - General Application Form: Newsletters: Ann Gifford, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - General Application Form: Newsletters: Brenda Reynolds, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - General Application Form: Newsletters: Money 2000: Barbara J. Bristow, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - General Application Form: Educational Publications: Barbara Bristow, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - General Application Form: New Professional Award: Dona H. Tyler, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - General Application Form: Written News: Virginia G. Houseknecht, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - General Application Form: Florence Hall Award: Tarasha Darden-McKoy, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 44)